Preliminary Guide to the Washington State University College of Engineering Research Division Correspondence, Minutes, Reports, and Speeches circa 1940s-1970
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Budget Allocations 1968-1969, Jan. 1, 1969 - Desk Copy (Box 21, Folder 1037)
- Sound Suppressor Hydraulic Model Test (Box 22, Folder 1038)
- Proposal for Sound Suppressor Hydraulic Model Test (Box 22, Folder 1039)
- Sound Suppressor Hydraulic Model Test (Box 22, Folder 1040)
- Radiocarbon Dating (Box 22, Folder 1041)
- Quantitative Spectrochemical Analyses (Box 22, Folder 1042)
- Thermal Conductivity of Plastic Refractory Products (Box 22, Folder 1043)
- Evaluation of Industrial Coatings (Box 22, Folder 1044)
- Heat Balance and Plant Cost Calculations on CO2 Magnesite Flue Dust Process (Box 22, Folder 1045)
- Carbon Dating of Geological Materials (Box 22, Folder 1046)
- Chemical and Spectrochemical Analysis of Potable Water (Box 22, Folder 1047)
- Carbon-14 Dating (Box 22, Folder 1048)
- Radiocarbon Age Date Charcoal Samples (Box 22, Folder 1049)
- Determination of Grinding Characteristics of Dolomite for Pigment and Paper Filler (Box 22, Folder 1050)
- Hydraulic Model Studies of Powerdale Dam (Box 22, Folder 1051)
- Arson Investigation (Box 22, Folder 1052)
- Evaluation of Experimental Roof Panels (Box 22, Folder 1053)
- Correlation of Strength Properties of One-inch Lumber (Box 22, Folder 1054)
- Stiffness of Three-Span Decks (Box 22, Folder 1055)
- Investigate Glue Problem (Box 22, Folder 1056)
- Calibration of Pygmy Current Meter Serial #610657 (Box 22, Folder 1057)
- Study of Stiffness and Strength of Redwood and Spruce Lock-Deck (Box 22, Folder 1058)
- Leaching and Chemical Tests on Fiber Containers for Pure Food and Drug Acceptance Purposes (Box 22, Folder 1059)
- Potlach Patent Proceeds (Box 22, Folder 1060)
- Evaluation of Lock-Deck Panels and Certification of Test Procedures (Box 22, Folder 1061)
- Hydraulic Model Studies of Sullivan Creek Dam (Box 22, Folder 1062)
- Pullman Police Det. *? (Box 22, Folder 1063)
- Determine BTU Value of Sewer Gas (Box 22, Folder 1064)
- Pullman Water Distribution Network Analysis (Box 22, Folder 1065)
- Police Investigation - Pullman (Box 22, Folder 1066)
- Investigate Design and Performance of Auto Afterburner (Box 22, Folder 1067)
- Extraction Studies of Saponin Cake (Box 22, Folder 1068)
- Police Investigation - Hit-Run (Box 22, Folder 1069)
- The Effect of Species on Resin Performance (Box 22, Folder 1070)
- Durability of Laminated Timber Bonded with Melurac (Box 22, Folder 1071)
- ASTM Standard on Clear Wood (Box 22, Folder 1072)
- Developing Information for a Book on Semi-Quantitative Spectrographic Analysis (Box 22, Folder 1073)
- Study on Spectrographic Techniques (Box 22, Folder 1074)
- Study on Polypropylane for Returnable Milk Bottles (Box 22, Folder 1075)
- Analyze Soil Moisture for Tritium Content (Box 22, Folder 1076)
- Model Studies of Iron Gate Project (Box 22, Folder 1077)
- Wells Comprehensive Model (Box 22, Folder 1078)
- Wells Hydrocombine Flume Model (Box 22, Folder 1079)
- Hydraulic Model Studies of Fish Passage Facilities, Wells Hydrocombine Project (Box 22, Folder 1080)
- Consultation on Carbon Dating (Box 22, Folder 1081)
- Fruit Canning Waste Treatment Study (Box 22, Folder 1082)
- Investigation of Brown Stain in Lumber (Box 22, Folder 1083)
- Stress Analysis of Trim Saw Mechanism (Box 22, Folder 1084)
- Evaluating Jack Pine and Tamarack Studs (Box 22, Folder 1085)
- Study of Extra-Terrestrial Radio Noise Effects (Box 22, Folder 1086)
- Study of Extra-Terrestrial Radio Noise Effects (Box 22, Folder 1087)
- Experimental Studies of the Fluid Mechanism Forces Producing Vibration in Transmission Line Conductors*? (Box 22, Folder 1088)
- Particleboards from Spent Pine Chips (Box 22, Folder 1089)
- Process One Wood Sample for C-14 Dating (Box 22, Folder 1090)
- Evaluation of Wax Emulsions for Particleboard (Box 22, Folder 1091)
- Clay Samples (Box 22, Folder 1092)
- Thermal Conductivity of Mullite Refractories (Box 22, Folder 1093)
- Kendrick, Idaho, Sewage Treatment Plant B.O.D. Study (Box 22, Folder 1094)
- Hydroelectrical Model for Rocky Reach Dam (Box 22, Folder 1095)
- Analysis of Water Distribution System Using Mcllroy Analyzer (Box 22, Folder 1096)
- Analysis of Cheney, Washington Water Distribution System with the Mcllroy Analyzer (Box 22, Folder 1097)
- Paint Problem (Box 22, Folder 1098)
- Earth Resistivity Investigations (Box 22, Folder 1099)
- Prepar Flakes (Box 22, Folder 1100)
- Range Forage Analysis (Box 22, Folder 1101)
- Investigation of Lumber Contamination (Box 22, Folder 1102)
- Exposure of Molded Fiber Products (Box 22, Folder 1103)
- **Rheological Study of Boron Nitride Thickened Silicone Greases (Box 22, Folder 1104)
- Rheological Flow Properties of Boron-Nitride Greases (Box 22, Folder 1105)
- Rheological Flow Properties of Boron-Nitride Greases (Box 22, Folder 1106)
- Study Agreement (Box 22, Folder 1107)
- Effects of Tension, Suspension System and Dumping on Static and **Dynamic Strains in Bluehird*? Conductor (Box 22, Folder 1108)
- Dynamic Test on Bluehird*? Conductor Using Measured Input Power (Box 22, Folder 1109)
- Photo Report of Setup for Fanner Manufacturing Company (Box 22, Folder 1110)
- Static and Dynamic Tests on Bluebird*? Conductor with and without Fanner Manufacturing Company II B Rods 1112 ** Dynamic Tests on Bluebrid*? Conductor with Single and Double Armor Rods (Box 22, Folder 1111)
- Investigate Explosion at Ferris High School (Box 22, Folder 1113)
- A Field Survey of Peach Soft Suture in the Pacific Northwest, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 1114)
- A Field Survey of Peach Soft Suture in the Pacific N.N. Second Edition) (Box 22, Folder 1115)
- A Field Survey of Peach Soft Suture in the Pacific N.H. (Contract and 1st.*? Extension) (Box 22, Folder 1116)
- Garfield County Density Testing (Box 22, Folder 1117)
- Gas Chromatology of Gaseous Sludge Lagoon Effluents (Box 22, Folder 1118)
- Development of Corrosion Resistant Anchor Red System: Progress Report #3 - Final Report (Box 22, Folder 1119)
- Rock Island Fish Attraction Facilities (Box 22, Folder 1120)
- Hydraulic Model Studies of the Rock Island Fish Attraction Facilities, Volume I (Box 22, Folder 1121)
- Hydraulic Model Studies of the Rock Island Fish Attraction Facilities, Volume II (Box 22, Folder 1122)
- Consultant Services: Chemical Slurry Pump Design and Lubrication (Box 22, Folder 1123)
- Budget Allocation 1961/62 - July 1, 1961 (Desk Copy) (Box 23, Folder 1124)
- Budget Allocation 1961/62 - July 1, 1961 (Including Section Originals) (Box 23, Folder 1125)
- Original Section Requests 1959-11961 Biennial Budget Requests (Box 23, Folder 1126)
- Biennium Budget Forecast and Appropriation 1959-1961 (Box 23, Folder 1127)
- Quarterly Cost and Income Reports 1958/59 (Box 23, Folder 1128)
- Quarterly Cost and Income Reports 1959/60 (Box 23, Folder 1129)
- 381 C12-13 (Box 23, Folder 1130)
- D-10 (Box 23, Folder 1131)
- 381 E (Box 23, Folder 1132)
- 381 E 13.3 59/60 Annual Review 61/62 (Box 23, Folder 1133)
- 381 E 13.4 (Box 23, Folder 1134)
- Cost and Income Report 1961/62 (Box 23, Folder 1135)
- 381 F1 (Box 23, Folder 1136)
- 381 F3 (Box 23, Folder 1137)
- 381 F4 (Box 23, Folder 1138)
- 381 F5 (Box 23, Folder 1139)
- 381 F8 (Box 23, Folder 1140)
- Comparison of Air Filters (Box 23, Folder 1141)
- Interpretation of Infrared Spectra (Box 23, Folder 1142)
- Calcium and Magnesium Determination on Barley Samples - Final Report (Box 23, Folder 1143)
- Soil and Forage Analysis - Final Report (Box 23, Folder 1144)
- Spectrographic Analysis of Plant Ash (Box 23, Folder 1145)
- Spectrographic Analysis of Plant Ash (Box 23, Folder 1146)
- Infrared Characterization of Experimental Samples (Box 23, Folder 1147)
- Analysis of Deionized Water from WSU Nuclear Reactor (Box 23, Folder 1148)
- Chemical Analyses (Box 23, Folder 1149)
- Examination of Gasoline Samples (Box 23, Folder 1150)
- Water Analyses (Box 23, Folder 1151)
- "How It Came Out" - April, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 1152)
- Washington State University Bulletin - Biennial Report 1962 (Box 24, Folder 1153)
- Business Cycle Developments - December 1962 (Box 24, Folder 1154)
- Business Cycle Developments - January 1963 (Box 24, Folder 1155)
- Know the Issues*? (Box 24, Folder 1156)
- Division of Industrial Research - Summary of 1962/63 Research Program from July 1, 1962 - April 1, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 1157)
- Original Submittals for 1963-65 Biennium Forecast (Box 24, Folder 1158)
- 1961/1963 Biennial Budget Exhibits (Box 24, Folder 1159)
- Budget - C.E. Dept. (Box 25, Folder 1160)
- Budget - Architectural Engineering (Box 25, Folder 1161)
- Budget - Mechanical Engineering - Current *? (Box 25, Folder 1162)
- Budget - 1957/59 (Box 25, Folder 1163)
- Budget - Material 29-36 (Box 25, Folder 1164)
- Budget - 1955/57 (Box 25, Folder 1165)
- Budget - April, May, June 1955 Interim Budget Allocations and Expenditures (Box 25, Folder 1166)
- Budget - 1951/53 Biennium (Box 25, Folder 1167)
- Budget - 1949/51 (Box 25, Folder 1168)
- Budget - 1949/51 (Box 25, Folder 1169)
- Biennial Report 1949-51 (Box 25, Folder 1170)
- Financial Report (Box 25, Folder 1171)
- Budgets - EEDEPT. 1947-49 (Box 25, Folder 1172)
- 1947-49 Budgets - College of Engineering (Box 25, Folder 1173)
- Budgets 1947-49 (Box 25, Folder 1174)
- Budgets - EEDEPT. 1945-47 (Box 25, Folder 1175)
- - 1943/45 - 1945/47 (Box 25, Folder 1176)
- Biennial Budgets - 1943-45 (Box 25, Folder 1177)
- Budget - EE 1943-45 (Box 25, Folder 1178)
- Budget - 1941-42/41/43 (Box 25, Folder 1179)
- Biennial Budgets - (1941-1943) (Box 25, Folder 1180)
- Budgets - 1940 (Box 25, Folder 1181)
- Budgets - 1938-1938 (Box 25, Folder 1182)
- Biennial Reports (1937-39) (Box 25, Folder 1183)
- Equipment Survey - S100 - EE, 1945 (Box 25, Folder 1184)
- ** Budgets - 1936-1937 + Ind (Box 25, Folder 1185)
- ECPD - 1950 Inspection (Box 25, Folder 1186)
- Budget - Division of Industrial Research (Box 25, Folder 1187)
- School of Mines - Budgets (Box 25, Folder 1188)
- Budget - Agricultural Engineering (Box 25, Folder 1189)
- Budget - Engineering Experiment Station (Box 25, Folder 1190)
- Accreditation - General (Box 25, Folder 1191)
- Manual of Inspection Procedure (Box 25, Folder 1192)
- Procedure for Review of Undergraduate Engineering Curricula (Box 25, Folder 1193)
- ECPD Accreditation 1954-55 (Box 25, Folder 1194)
- Procedure for Review of Undergraduate Engineering Curricula (Box 25, Folder 1195)
- ECPD Accreditation - 1950 Agricultural Engineering Dpartment (Box 25, Folder 1196)
- ECPD Accreditation - 1950 Architectural Engineeering Department (Box 25, Folder 1197)
- ECDP Accreditation - 1950/1953 Chemical Engineering Department (Box 25, Folder 1198)
- ECDP Accreditation - 1950 Chemical Engineering Department (Box 25, Folder 1199)
- ECDP Accreditation - 1950 Electrical Engineering Department (Box 25, Folder 1200)
- ECDP Accreditation - 1950 Mechanical Engineering Department (Box 25, Folder 1201)
- ECDP Accreditation - 1937-1941 (Box 25, Folder 1202)
- Procedure for Periodic Review of Accredited Engineering Curricula - State College of Washington 1941 (Box 25, Folder 1203)
- Procedure for Periodic Review of Accredited Engineering Curricula H.S.C. 1941 (Box 25, Folder 1204)
- Procedure for Periodic Review of Accredited Engineering Curricula - Electrical Engineering (Box 25, Folder 1205)
- Accrediting Procedures of Committee on Engineering Schools of the Engineer's Council for Professional Development - The State College of Washington (Box 25, Folder 1206)
- G.E. Scholarships - 1956-57 (Box 25, Folder 1207)
- President - Appropriations - Legislative (Box 25, Folder 1208)
- Ten Year Report - STS - 1955-1956 - Schools of Mines (Box 25, Folder 1209)
- Ten Year Report Electrical Engineering and College of Engineering (Box 25, Folder 1210)
- Ten Year Report Department of Civil Engineering- 1935 (Box 25, Folder 1211)
- Reports - Annual and Biennial (Box 25, Folder 1212)
- Report on the Department of Agricultural Engineering -State College of Washington - March, 1937 (Box 25, Folder 1213)
- Applied Research Activities and Equipment - 1949 (Box 25, Folder 1214)
- Report I - The Division of Industrial Research - State College of Washington 4-1-45 to 12-31-45 (Box 25, Folder 1215)
- Report of Activities of the Washington State Institute of Technology - October 1948 to October 1949 (Box 25, Folder 1216)
- Architectural Engineering - General (Box 26, Folder 1217)
- Chemical Engineering - General through 1963 (Box 26, Folder 1218)
- Civil Engineering - General through 1963 (Box 26, Folder 1219)
- Electrical Engineering - General through 1963 (Box 26, Folder 1220)
- Bureau of Reclamation Res. Contract (Box 26, Folder 1221)
- Hydroquinone (Box 26, Folder 1222)
- Technical Literature Review on Hydroquinone (Box 26, Folder 1223)
- Evaluation of Trashrack Design Criteria (Box 26, Folder 1224)
- Water Temperature in Fish Rearing Facilities (Box 26, Folder 1225)
- Hydraulic Engineering Investigation for Design of Rocky Reach Power Unit Trashracks (Box 26, Folder 1226)
- A Report on the Clark County Road System - 1967 (Box 26, Folder 1227)
- Clark County Road Program Evaluation (Box 26, Folder 1228)
- Evaluation Program on Use of Copper Sheets as Overlay for Building Material (Box 26, Folder 1229)
- Thermal Hydraulic Pilot Models and Studies of the Columbia River (Box 26, Folder 1230)
- Thermal Hydraulic Pilot Model Studies of the Columbia River (Box 26, Folder 1231)
- Preliminary Acoustical Study of an Experimental Polymeric Material (Box 26, Folder 1232)
- Airborne Sound Transmission Loss (Box 26, Folder 1233)
- Airborne Sound Transmission Loss Study (Box 26, Folder 1234)
- Chemicals for Forests Products Phases 2 and 3 (Box 26, Folder 1235)
- Chemicals for Forests Products (Box 26, Folder 1236)
- Tolerance of Vegetation to Sulphur Dioxide Fumigation (Box 26, Folder 1237)
- Asphalt Research (Box 26, Folder 1238)
- Polymer Grafting to Inorganic Materials (Box 26, Folder 1239)
- Benton County Road System Study (Box 26, Folder 1240)
- Study of Transmission Line Radio Noise Problems (Box 26, Folder 1241)
- Theoretical and Experimental Studies of the Vortex Shedding Action on Vibratory Cylinders (Box 26, Folder 1242)
- Theoretical and Experimental Studies of the Fluid Mechanical Forces Producing Vibration in Transmission Line Conductors (Box 26, Folder 1243)
- Synopsis of Lift, Drag, and Vortex Frequency for Rigid Circular Cylinders (Box 26, Folder 1244)
- Conducting Research in Transmission Line Conductor Vibration Problems (Box 26, Folder 1245)
- 261 - 271 (Box 27, Folder 1246)
- Mechanisms by Which Germanium Affects the Electrolytic Deposition of Zinc (Box 27, Folder 1247)
- 274 Studies on Oyster Culture (Box 27, Folder 1248)
- Motor Vehicle Tax Money Allocation Among Counties (Box 27, Folder 1249)
- 277 - 291 (Box 27, Folder 1250)
- Noxon Hydroelectric Power Model (Box 27, Folder 1251)
- Disconnect Switches During Conditions Test - Bonneville (Box 27, Folder 1252)
- 297 - Upward (Box 27, Folder 1253)
- V-Notch Drain Tile Test (Box 27, Folder 1254)
- A Resilient Flooring and Surfacing Composition (Box 27, Folder 1255)
- Concrete Masonry Investigation (Box 27, Folder 1256)
- Carbon - Survey of Industrial Carbon Requirements of the Pacific Northwest (Box 27, Folder 1257)
- Concrete Pipe News (Box 27, Folder 1258)
- Relation of Shrinkage to Moisture Content in Concrete Masonry Units (Box 27, Folder 1259)
- Recommendations for Concrete Masonry (Box 27, Folder 1260)
- Washington, D.C. (Box 29, Folder 1261)
- Exterior Coatings (Box 29, Folder 1262)
- ** Chem. (Box 29, Folder 1263)
- Liquid Air Heat Exlumbre Heads (Blueprint) (Box 30, Folder 1264)
- Bryan Hall P.A. (Blueprint) (Box 30, Folder 1265)
- Abacortes Chamber of Commerce (Box 31, Folder 1266)
- Tacoma Air Pollution Study (Box 31, Folder 1267)
- Walla Walla Chamber of Commerce (Box 31, Folder 1268)
- Grand Coulee Public Schools (Box 31, Folder 1269)
- Lewiston-Clarkston Air Quality Survey - 1962 (Box 32, Folder 1270)
- An Air Pollution Study in the Lewiston-Clarkston Area (Box 32, Folder 1271)
- An Air Pollution Study in the Lewiston-Clarkston Area (Box 32, Folder 1272)
- The Causes of Air Pollution in a "One Industry" Community (Box 32, Folder 1273)
- A Source Inventory Study in the Vicinity of Lewiston, Idaho, and Clarkston, Washington August 20, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 1274)
- Analysis of French Fried Potatoes (Box 32, Folder 1275)
- Water Extraction Studies on Redwood (Box 32, Folder 1276)
- Oil Circuit Breaker Line Dropping Study (Box 32, Folder 1277)
- Circuit Breaker Test (Box 32, Folder 1278)
- Arson Investigation (Box 32, Folder 1279)
- Water Analysis (Box 32, Folder 1280)
- Chemicals for Forest Products (Box 32, Folder 1281)
- Information for Patent Application (Box 32, Folder 1282)
- Radiocarbon Dating of Archeological Material (Box 32, Folder 1283)
- Aswan Dam Carbon-14 Dating (Box 32, Folder 1284)
- Arson Investigation (Box 32, Folder 1285)
- Water Distribution Study for East Spokane Water District #1 (Box 32, Folder 1286)
- Study on Composition of Coal Ash (Box 32, Folder 1287)
- Analysis of Coal Ash Samples 57250, 57263 and 57264 (Box 32, Folder 1288)
- Analysis of Coal Ash Samples 57215 and 57244 (Box 32, Folder 1289)
- Effects of a Phase Change on the Propagation of Finite Amplitude Wave (Box 32, Folder 1290)
- High Frequency Radio Propagation Studies (Box 32, Folder 1291)
- Comparison of Pyrolytic Graphite and Standard Graphite for ** Elec. in Spec. Ana. (Box 32, Folder 1292)
- Tally A. Grease (Box 32, Folder 1293)
- Water Analysis (Box 32, Folder 1294)
- Geophysical Studies for U.S. Corps of Engineers (Box 32, Folder 1295)
- Pulp Industrial Odor Control (Box 32, Folder 1296)
- Pulp Industrial Odor Control (Box 32, Folder 1297)
- A Manual for Direct Gas Chromatographic Analysis of Sulphur Gasses in Process Streams (Box 32, Folder 1298)
- Application of Instrumentation to Pulp Mill Atmospheric Discharges (Box 32, Folder 1299)
- Methods for the Determination of Sulphur Compounds in Pulp Mill Effluent Gasses (Box 32, Folder 1300)
- Gas Chromatographic Analysis of Hydrogen Sulfide, Sulfur Dioxide, Mercaptans and Alkyl Sulfides and Disulfides (Box 32, Folder 1301)
- Progress Report on Studies on the Analyses of Pulp Gases Final Report on Absorption of Odor Producing Sulfur (Box 32, Folder 1302)
- Compounds to National Council for Stream Improvement Preliminary Estimation of Recoverable Waste Heat from the Kraft Pulping Process (Box 32, Folder 1303)
- Thesis on Absorption of Hydrogen Sulfide and Methyl Mercaptan from Dilute Gas Mixtures (Box 32, Folder 1304)
- Examination of Wood Chips for Foreign Matter Gas Chromatography Applied to Atmospheric Kraft Odors (Box 32, Folder 1305)
- Sphaerotilus Control for Irrigation Water (Box 32, Folder 1306)
- Analysis of Gasoline (Box 32, Folder 1307)
- Spectrochemical Analysis of Electrolytic Solutions (Box 32, Folder 1308)
- Analize Sample of Soil for Trace Elements (Box 32, Folder 1309)
- Study Use of Vaughn Chopper Pump on Pulp Chips (Box 32, Folder 1310)
- Research on Low Calorie, High Energy Food (Box 32, Folder 1311)
- Drum Drying Tests on Raspberries and Apples (Box 32, Folder 1312)
- Drum Drying Apple and Raspberry Pulp (Box 32, Folder 1313)
- Platinum Group Analysis (Box 32, Folder 1314)
- Arson Investigation (Box 32, Folder 1315)
- A Collection Technique for Separation of Aerosol and Gaseous Herbicides (Box 32, Folder 1316)
- Portable Sampler Herbicide Analysis Report (Box 32, Folder 1319)
- ** An Investigation of Atmospheric Drift and from of 2,4-D (Box 32, Folder 1320)
- Spectrochemical Analysis of Food Sample (Box 32, Folder 1321)
- Analysis of Bone, Water and Feed Samples (Box 32, Folder 1322)
- Spectrographic Analysis Feed Samples (Box 32, Folder 1323)
- Spectrographic Analysis of Feed Supplement (Box 32, Folder 1324)
- Spectrographic Analysis (Box 32, Folder 1325)
- Spectrochemical Analysis of Algae Waste (Box 32, Folder 1326)
- **IR Analysis of Lamb Flavor Samples (Box 32, Folder 1327)
- Investigation of Chicken Extracts (Box 32, Folder 1328)
- Radiocarbon Age Date Ocean Sediments (Box 32, Folder 1329)
- Radiocarbon Age Date Charcoal Samples (Box 32, Folder 1330)
- Water Analysis (Box 32, Folder 1331)
- Radiochemical Analysis of Soil Samples (Box 32, Folder 1332)
- Analysis of Rumen for Volatile A (Box 32, Folder 1333)
- Carbon Dating of Archeological Specimen (Box 32, Folder 1334)
- **Pozzolanic Material Analysis (Box 32, Folder 1335)
- Investigation of Refrigerator Compressor Oils (Box 32, Folder 1336)
- Radiocarbon Dating (Box 32, Folder 1337)
- Tally A. Grease (Box 32, Folder 1338)
- Spectrochemical Analysis of Egg Ash (Box 32, Folder 1339)
- WSU Building and Grounds (Box 32, Folder 1340)
- Spectrochemical Analysis of Water (Box 32, Folder 1341)
- Spectrochemical Analysis of Plant Ash (Box 32, Folder 1342)
- Liophilization of Potato Samples (Box 32, Folder 1343)
- Radio Direction Finding Equipment (Box 32, Folder 1344)
- Carbon Dating - Alaskan Project (Soc. and Anthro.) (Box 32, Folder 1345)
- Use of Tritated Material to Elucidate Nuclear Conditions (Plant Pathology) (Box 32, Folder 1346)
- Analysis of Ca, Na (Box 32, Folder 1347)
- Chemical Treatment for Preservation of Important Documents (Box 32, Folder 1348)
- Fluoride Analysis of Peach Leaves (Agronomy) (Box 32, Folder 1349)
- Spectral Study of Arc Discharge (Box 32, Folder 1350)
- Spectral Study of Arc Discharge (Box 32, Folder 1351)
- Carbon Dating of Archeological Samples (Box 32, Folder 1352)
- Neutron Activation Analysis Tagging of Onion Smuts (Box 32, Folder 1353)
- Chemical Analysis of Corrosion Residue and Consulting (Box 32, Folder 1354)
- Analysis of Animal Hair for Inorganic Elements (Box 32, Folder 1355)
- Radiocarbon Dating of Charcoal Samples (Box 32, Folder 1356)
- Carbon Dating - Marmes Rock Rhelter (Box 32, Folder 1357)
- Carbon Dating - Little Goose (Box 32, Folder 1358)
- Investigation of a Rubber Gasket (Box 32, Folder 1359)
- Investigation of Turbine Oil (Box 32, Folder 1360)
- Investigation of Steam Condensate Odor Problems (Box 32, Folder 1361)
- Analysis of Paint for Presence of Lead (Box 32, Folder 1362)
- Spectrochemical Analysis of Egg Ash (Box 32, Folder 1363)
- **Feed and Feed Supplement Ana. (Box 32, Folder 1364)
- Comparison of Two Cleaners (Box 32, Folder 1365)
- Chemical and Spectrochemical Analysis of Feed Samples (Box 32, Folder 1366)
- Spectrochemical Analysis of Cb Metal (Box 32, Folder 1367)
- Spectrochemical Analysis of Water, Feed and Biological Samples (Box 32, Folder 1368)
- Analysis of Mineral Supplement for Manganese (Box 32, Folder 1369)
- Police Investigation (Box 32, Folder 1370)
- Analysis of Animal Hair Samples for Inorganic Elements (Box 32, Folder 1371)
- Analysis of Sediment in distilled Water (Box 32, Folder 1372)
- Arson Investigation, WSU (Box 32, Folder 1373)
- Arson Investigation (Box 32, Folder 1374)
- Analysis of Feed, Soil, and Mineral Supplement Samples (Box 32, Folder 1375)
- Spectrographic Analysis of Manganese Modules (Box 32, Folder 1376)
- Preliminary Design and Cost Estimate on Custom Spectrograph (Box 32, Folder 1377)
- Investigation of Turbine Oil (B. and G.) (Box 32, Folder 1378)
- Thermal Column Water Wall (Reactor) (Box 32, Folder 1379)
- Archeological Applications of Radiations (Anthropology) (Box 32, Folder 1380)
- Momentum Apparatus (Civil Engineering) (Box 32, Folder 1381)
- Development of Procedures in Radiochemistry (Box 32, Folder 1382)
- **Milk Vacuum Bottles Exp. Dairy - Blosser (Box 32, Folder 1383)
- Use of Infra-red Equipment (Department of Chemistry) (Box 32, Folder 1384)
- Analysis of Compressor Air (Box 32, Folder 1385)
- Police Investigation: Hit-Run Comparison of Paint (Box 32, Folder 1386)
- Study of Communication Equipment (Box 32, Folder 1387)
- Police Investigation Hit-Run (Box 32, Folder 1388)
- Police Investigation Hit-Run (Box 32, Folder 1389)